- **** +971-506831025
- ✓ shahnaina1998@gmail.com
- Y Karama , Dubai



Personal Skills

- Flexible, Ample problem-solving abilities, willingness to learn new tasks. Experienced in communicating with the creative team and clients. Well-organized with an ability to prioritize tasks.
- .Knowledge of windows based Package System and Windows Server System.

Career Objectives

Seeking a key role in a growth-oriented organization where i can utilize my knowledge and experience together with my innovation and versatility and my ability to work well with others.

Professional Skills

4+ years of real time experience in coding websites and applications using modern HTML5, CSS3 and Javascript. Most of the Website that I have worked are CMS based even that there will be an HTML development before theming. I can create website in HTML5 with all web standards, SEO and CMS friendly.

- HTML5, CSS3, React JS, Javascript ES6, C, C++, Java, Node jS, Source control, SCSS, LESS, jquery, Bootstrap, Adobe XD, Photoshop, Illustrator.
- Content Management systems: Sitecore, wordPress, Magento, Drupal
- Development Frameworks: ASP.NET, Wordpress, Magento, Concrete5.
- Databases: Microsoft SQL Server, MongoDB.
- Tools: VS Code, Microsoft visual studio.
- Source control systems: Git, Microsoft TFS.

Education Qualification

Bachelor Of Engineering: Computer Science Engineering from RGPV, Bhopal, India(2012-2016)

PLUS TWO: A.K.H.S School (2012)
Class x: A.K.H.S. School (2010)

Professional Experience

• I have done work as a freelancer from February 2021 to October 2021. I provided projects to my clients at that time like food ordering website, blogger website and stationary website.

Techies IT Solutions pvt. Ltd

Gwalior June 2016 to January 2021

UI/Web Developer

- Translating designs and wireframes into high quality code. Developing the latest user-facing features using React.js. Workflow tools included: HTML5, CSS3, React Js, Bootstrap, jQuery, Bitbucket, Git, WordPress and Sitecore Front-end Development. Knowledge of some SEO principles. Collaborate with back-end developers and designers to improve usability. Bringing mock-ups to life using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript. Web page development from design to code and up to production deployment. Optimize website performance using latest technology. Maintaining an organized workflow using a project management tool (Git, Microsoft TFS.). Communicating technical issues in an understandable manner to the team and clients.
- Workflow tools included: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, jQuery, Bitbucket, Git, Concrete 5
 framework. Web page development from design to test and up to production deployment.
- Optimize website performance using latest technology.
- Creating wireframe, designing website, UI/UX Designs, front end development (HTML, CSS), Designing banners, working with the US Marketing Team to plan and implement designs and digital marketing potential.

Projects

- Developed an interactive tourism web application in an agile team environment by deploying HTML5,CSS and javascript.
- By using HTML,CSS ,Bootstrap & Javascript to create websites like Redstore and food order

 website
- Design and establish user friendly website OMNIFOOD that uses AI to create and deliver custom healthy meal plans.

Personal Details

Name :Naina shah

Date of birth :25-07-1994

Sex :Female

Nationality: :Indian

Religion : Hindu

Visa status :Visit visa

Marital status :Married

Language known : English & Hindi